bad-dragon.com 2013-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Bad Dragon

Bad Dragon is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of customers who buy from us. For visitors, we've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. For customers, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Bad Dragon unless indicated otherwise.

The Bad Dragon website conforms to the requirements of the Data Protection Act, 1998.

### Visitors to our Website - what information do we collect?

When you visit our website, our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your IP Address, your browser type and version, your locally configured language and locale, and the pages within our web site that you visit.  
We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can sture in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the website can tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes.  
We may aggregate information collected from other Websites in order to better tailor our website and products to your interests.

### Members of our Website - what information do we collect?

When you visit our website and log in as a registered member, our web server collects additional information about you, including your email address, your nickname and your favorite species.  
If you use our Address Book functionality, our website will also collect your shipping and billing addresses and your contact phone number. If you elect to use our online Forums, it will also collect messages, comments and private messages submitted via the forums.  
If you use our customer services ticketing system, it will also collect messages, tickets and attachments submitted via our ticket system. If you email us, our website will collect the contents, subject line and other information relating to emails you send us.

### Purchasers on our Website - what information do we collect?

When you make a purchase through our website, our web server collects additional information about you, including product purchase and order history and payment transaction IDs. **We do not store financial information (credit card numbers, CVV code, etc) for any reason.**

### Visitors from advertisements on other websites - what information do we collect?

When you click on an advertisement for Bad Dragon on another website, our web server collects additional information about you, including the name of the website you were visiting, the URL of the page you were viewing before clicking on the advertisement, and the content of the advertisement you clicked on. We may also collect information regarding how many times an advertisement was shown to you before you clicked on it.

### How is information collected?

Information is collected via the following methods:

  * Information gathered from browsing our website
  * Information submitted when you register for a Bad Dragon account
  * Information submitted when you place an order with us
  * Information submitted when you contact us via our ticket system
  * Information submitted when you send us an email, or phone us
  * Information gathered from advertising publishers via ‘inbound links’, when you visit our website by clicking on an advertisement on another website

### Who do we share data with, and why?

We share data for the purpose of providing services to you, such as manufacturing and shipping your order.

**Shipping Companies**  
We share your name and shipping address, order number, the value of your order and (for orders outside the US) the contents of your order with our shipping providers. We do this in order to deliver your order to you, to allow you to track your order while it is being shipped, and to comply with Customs regulations.

**Payment Providers**  
We share your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, financial information including credit card information (we do not store this ourselves), your order number and the value of your order with our payment providers. We do this in order to process payment for your order.

**Email Newsletter Providers**  
We share your nickname, email address, the types of newsletter you’re interested in receiving and your favorite species with our email newsletter providers. We do this in order to organize and send newsletters to you about Bad Dragon products and services.

**Advertising providers**  
We share your IP address, shipping city, shipping state, shipping country, order ID, shipping cost and order value with our advertising providers. We do this in order to facilitate the processing of advertising commission payments, and to serve geographically targeted adverts on other website. Important note: This information is not shared with websites upon which adverts are displayed; it’s shared only with the advertising network.

### When would we disclose this information?

We may disclose this information in order to perform the tasks listed above in ‘Who do we share data with, and why?’.

We will not disclose customer personal and account information to others, unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of Bad Dragon, our customers, or others, or where Bad Dragon has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.

Bad Dragon also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties personally identifiable customer information. The circumstances under which Bad Dragon will disclose such personally identifiable information are when:

  * It is necessary in order to provide service to the customer;
  * It is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of Bad Dragon and its customers;
  * It is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that Bad Dragon determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable;
  * It is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by Bad Dragon and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.

### What do we use this information for?

We use this information for a number of purposes, including generating statistics and reports on website activity and improving our website. We use it for the purposes of marketing, to facilitate the sending of targeted newsletters promoting Bad Dragon products you may be interested in, improving the content and relevancy of our advertisements, and tailoring the content of our website to your interests. We also use this information for the purpose of order fulfillment, to obtain and manufacture items on your order, to ship and deliver your order, to contact you in the event of a problem with your order, and to contact you to update you on the progress of your order.

You may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or notices of new or enhanced products, services or related services from Bad Dragon by clicking on the ‘opt out’ link within email newsletters sent to you. You may opt out of newsletters at any time.

Please note, however, that Bad Dragon reserves the right to send information directly relevant to your order and Bad Dragon account at our discretion; this is to allow us to fulfil your order and to deal with any problems with your order or account which may occur. You may request that your entire account (and all personally identifiable information) be deleted by submitting a ticket, listing your email address and reason for removal using our contact form.
